PRAJUL N A S

Linkedin.com/in/prajulnas

nasprajul@gmail.com 7356026361|Thrissur, Kerala

B-Tech from Christ College of Engineering with specialization in Electrical and Electronics Engineering with basic knowledge in programing and in learning stage. I can utilize and apply my knowledge, skills which would enable me as a fresh graduate to grow while fulfilling organizational goals.

WORK EXPERIENCE

WIPRO TECHNOLOGIES

Jan 2022 - Aug 2022

Phone Banking Associate, Kochi

- Working as phone banking representative at RAK Bank, UAE (The National Bank of Ras Al Khaimah)
- Handling 80+ customers a day; dealing general queries, bank product information and transaction related details and problems at banking level.

AMAZON DEVELOPMENT CENTRE INDIA

Sep 2020 - Mar 2021

Customer Service Associate, Coimbatore

- Working with 50+ customers a day; solving product and purchase related problems at an enterprise level.
- Awarded Top performer of month for helping valuable customers with appropriate solutions in December.

EDUCATION

B-Tech, Electrical and Electronics Engineering - Christ College Of Engineering, Irinjalakuda

2015 - 2019

- Aggregate CGPA of 6.82.
- Served as College Union Chairman in 2016-2017

12th State Board - G.F HSS, Nattika

2013 - 2015

- Science with Computer. Scored 80% in total.

PROJECTS & INTERNSHIPS

- Project Work:
 - **ETO STERLIZER**: Designed and assembled Ethylene oxide sterilizer which is used to sterilize medical and pharmaceutical products that cannot support conventional high temperature steam sterilization. Submitted to APJ Abdul Kalam Technological University.
- Internships: Transform Electricals, Bangalore
 - Participated in assembling of power transformers, servo stabilizers and earthing transformers.
 - Gained knowledge on aspects such as Electrical circuits, Components and Estimation of product cost.

TRAINING & WORKSHOPS

- Certification Courses:
 - C Programing and Computational Thinking

2021

AutoCAD, Proteus8 and Revit Professional (Truebit Technologies)

2018

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- **Coding:** C, C++ Intermediate level
- **AutoCAD:** 2D Drawings Beginner level
- MS Office: Word, Excel, Power Point Intermediate level